# AAKANKSHA PATIL



## CONTACT

9890756103

aakankshapatil366@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/aakankshapatil-a612a124b

Navi mumbai, India

### SKILLS

#### soft skills

- Communication
- · Leadership skills
- · Teamwork and collaboration
- · Problem solving
- · Time management
- · Technical skills
- Project management

#### technical skills

- Python
- React
- Html/Css
- Java
- Javascript
- Database : mongodb /sqlLinux Operating System

## **EDUCATION**

• DIPLOMA

Institute of Technology (Polytechnic) Navi Mumbai, Mumbai, Maharashtra,

India,

05/2019 - 04/2021 information technology

82.94%

BTECH-IT

**Bharati Vidyapeeth College of** 

**Engineering** 

Navi Mumbai, Mumbai, Maharashtra,

India

9.80 CGPA

01/2024- 05/2024

Information technology.

• 10TH STANDARD

S. G. S. Highschool Girad Rd, Pachora, Maharashtra

04/2016 - 03/2017

74.40%

# **PROFILE**

I am looking for a responsible and challenging position with opportunities to enrich my knowledge and skills while contributing to the success of the organisation and building result-oriented professional growth. I am seeking a beginner role to enhance and explore my technical knowledge gained in the last three years. I am currently pursuing a B.Tech. degree from Bharati Vidyapeeth College of Engineering.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

## • Intenship

#### BHARAT INTERN

06/2023 -07/2023

Task - Portfolio, Temperature converter, Homepage of Netflix

Programming language: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript

#### SILMATES PVT.LTD.VADODARA

07/2023 -09/2023

Task - Solar Tracking System (Server Software)

Programming language: React.jsx, node.js, javascript (Linux)

### **BRIDGELABZ MUMBAI**

25/04/2024

Task - Basic and logical Programing Practice

Programming language: Python

### PERSONAL PROJECTS

## **I-FARMING WEBSITE (2021)**

• S/W -

Operating system: Android, windows

User interface: HTML, CSS

Programming language: Database oracle 10g

• H/W -

Processor: Intel i3,i5

Hard disk: 500GB,16gb (Internal storage)

Ram: 1 GB or more

#### E-MEDS WEBSITE (2023)

• S/W -

Operating system: Android, windows 11

User interface: HTML5, CSS

Programming language : Python-Django

• H/W -

Processor: AMD

Hard disk: Ryzen 5 5600U with Radeon Graphics

Ram: 1 GB or more

## SELF PORTFOLIO WEBSITE (2023)

• S/W -

Operating system : Android, windows 11 User interface : HTML5, CSS Programming language : Javascript

## TEMPERATURE CONVERTER (2023)

• S/W -

Operating system : Android, windows 11
User interface : HTML5, CSS
Programming language : Javascript

# **CERTIFICATES**

Programming with python (05/2022-06/2022)
 Basics of html/css (05/2023-05/2023)

• Basics of javascript programming (05/2022-06/2022)

• Business Analytics With Excel (05/2023-06/20223)

.....

# **LANGUAGES**

English	
Hindi	
Marathi	

# **INTERESTS**

- · Dancing
- · Book reading
- Chess
- · Cycling
- Travelling

------

# PERSONAL DETAILS

Name : Aakanksha Dharanj patil

Data of birth : 25/12/2001 Gender : Female Marital Status : Unmarried Nationality : Indian

-----

# **DECLARATION**

I can promise you that the information you've read above is accurate to the best of my knowledge, and I eagerly await your response. I'm grateful.

Yours sincerely Aakanksha patil